<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Steward Medicine</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ance_1">Here is a general outline on acne and how to treat it.</string>
    <string name="ance_2">KEY POINT: remember that pimples tend to come and go over a 4-6 week time frame. Treating the acne today does not make the current pimples go away. Instead, the treatments you put on today prevent the future pimples from starting. So it takes at least 4-6 weeks of treatment to start seeing results.</string>
    <string name="acne_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/C5Co4czoo5s" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="heart_agina_1">** IMPORTANT **</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_2">• If you are worried that you may be having a heart attack, call 9-1-1 immediately or go to the closest Emergency Department.</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_3">• Do NOT waste valuable time by going to your family doctor’s office.</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_4">• TIME IS CRUCIAL. Too often, patients waste valuable time by waiting to book an appointment with their family doctor, or walking in to their family doctor’s office. Instead, go to the ER directly!</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_5">WHAT IS HEART DISEASE?</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_6">Your heart is a muscle that gets energy from blood carrying oxygen. Your heart needs a constant supply of blood to keep working properly. Coronary artery disease develops when a combination of fatty materials and scar tissue (called “plaque”) builds up in the blood vessels that supply blood to your heart. The plaque buildup narrows the arteries and prevents the heart from getting enough blood.</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_7">Here are a few brief videos to help explain heart attacks and angina:</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_8">THE FOLLOWING ARE SIGNS OF HAVING A HEART ATTACK:</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_9">(click the picture for even more information)</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_10">FOR MORE INFORMATION:</string>
    <string name="heart_agina_11">Check out the Heart &amp; Stroke Foundation’s website.</string>
    <string name="heart_attack_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LA2DuxCcO4g" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="angina_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7PsDK2R95Sg" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="heart_attack_symptoms_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/o3RFrAKD1O4" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="angina_and_chest_pains_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5ClUXbLpu1M" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_1">WHY YOU DON\&apos;T NEED AN ANNUAL PHYSICAL:</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_2">• The old &quot;Annual Physical&quot; used to be a visit when the doctor could review your file to ensure that all routine tests were up to date.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_3">• With the computers in our office, we always have reminders that tell us when your tests are overdue. Therefore, an “Annual Physical” is no longer required for this purpose.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_4">• The “Annual Physical” was also a time for a complete ‘head-to-toe’ examination. However, research has shown that this type of exam does not provide any benefit.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_5">• Sometimes, people confuse the term “Annual Physical” with exams like their “PAP smear” test. Please note that these are not the same thing. Women from 21 to 70 years of age should still have a PAP smear test every three years, or yearly if you have ever had an abnormal PAP smear in the past.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_6">&quot;MORE&quot; IS NOT ALWAYS BETTER ...</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_7">Also, CLICK HERE for more information on why physicals are no longer suggested.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_8">INSTEAD OF ASKING TO BOOK A &quot;PHYSICAL&quot; ...</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_9">• Ask to book a visit for a specific concern(s) that you may have.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_10">• Ask if you have any blood work, tests, or cancer screens that are overdue. These can often be booked without actually seeing your doctor.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_11">• Ask to book a visit for a PAP test if that is what you are specifically concerned about.</string>
    <string name="annual_phyical_12"> or  of the same. **</string>
    <string name="annual_physical_video"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8c7qTsVVxXw" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="asthma_1">WHAT IS ASTHMA?</string>
    <string name="asthma_2">The symptoms of asthma include:</string>
    <string name="asthma_3">• Shortness of breath</string>
    <string name="asthma_4">• Tightness in the chest</string>
    <string name="asthma_5">• Coughing</string>
    <string name="asthma_6">• Wheezing.</string>
    <string name="asthma_7">Click here for even more information on “What is asthma?”</string>
    <string name="asthma_8">HOW DO YOU TREAT ASTHMA?</string>
    <string name="asthma_9">• Inhaled (puffer) medications. (See below for more information on puffers).</string>
    <string name="asthma_10">• Sometimes, for specific cases of asthma, your doctor may prescribe oral medications, like Singulair.</string>
    <string name="asthma_11">HOW DO THE PUFFERS HELP YOUR ASTHMA?</string>
    <string name="asthma_12">There are 2 main types of puffer medications:</string>
    <string name="asthma_13">1) <u>Bronchodilators</u>: these medications <i>dilate</i> your airways. In there words, they relax them; they open them up; they make them <i>wider</i> or <i>larger</i>. This allows you to breathe more air into your lungs. Bronchodilator medications are a quick “rescue” help for your asthma. They make you feel better quickly, but only temporarily.  They do not prevent the underlying inflammation that causes asthma attacks.</string>
    <string name="asthma_14">Click here for more information on these “rescue” puffers.</string>
    <string name="asthma_15">2) <u>Inhaled Steroids</u>: these decrease the <i>inflammation</i> in your airways. They get at the root cause of asthma. They take time (days to weeks) to take effect and they must be taking regularly every day in order to help you.</string>
    <string name="asthma_16">Click here for more information on inhaled steroid puffers. </string>
    <string name="asthma_17">The following video nicely explains how these two types of puffers work. The video is intended for children, but it still shows clear and useful information for adults too!:</string>
    <string name="asthma_18">HOW DO YOU TAKE YOUR PUFFERS?</string>
    <string name="asthma_19">HOW DO YOU KNOW IF YOUR ASTHMA IS UNDER CONTROL?</string>
    <string name="asthma_20">The goals of asthma control are:</string>
    <string name="asthma_21">• Requiring your “reliever” (“rescue”) inhalers as little as possible – 3 or less times per WEEK.</string>
    <string name="asthma_22">• <u>Never</u> having asthma symptoms at night.</string>
    <string name="asthma_23">• Your asthma is <u>not</u> affecting your physical activity or ability to exercise.</string>
    <string name="asthma_24">• Flares of your asthma are mild and infrequent.</string>
    <string name="asthma_25">• You <u>never</u> have to miss school nor work because of your asthma.</string>
    <string name="asthma_26">*** If you are not meeting ALL the above goals, then your asthma is NOT under proper control and you should return to see your doctor or health care provider. ***</string>
    <string name="asthma_27">FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT THE FOLLOWING WEBSITES:</string>
    <string name="asthma_28">The Asthma Society of Canada</string>
    <string name="asthma_29">The Canadian Thoracic Society</string>
    <string name="asthma_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7EDo9pUYvPE" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="asthma_vid_2"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Et_alsghel8" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_1">Benzodiazepines (also known as “benzos“) are a type of medication that some people take for sleep, anxiety, or relaxation.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_2">Here are the names of some commonly prescribed benzodiazepines, or similar types of medications:</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_3">• Alprazolam (“Xanax”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_4">• Chlordiazepoxide (“Librium”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_5">• Clobazam (“Frisium”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_6">• Diazepam (“Valium”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_7">• Lorazepam (“Ativan”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_8">• Nitrazepam (“Nitrazadon”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_9">• Oxazepam (“Serax” or “Zapex”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_10">• Temazepam (“Restoril”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_11">• Triazolam (“Halcion”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_12">• Zopiclone (“Imovane”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_13">• Zolpidem (“Ambien”)</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_14">Often people start taking these medications on an “as needed” basis. However, over time, people often start taking them more and more and unfortunately start taking them <i>regularly</i> every day or night. This is because these medications can cause ADDICTION and DEPENDENCE.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_15">For people who take these medications to help sleep, they start to forget how to sleep naturally on their own.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_16">These medications are also not recommended for long term treatment of anxiety.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_17">Click here for even more information.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_18">THESE MEDICATIONS CAUSE HARM:</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_19">• 5 times greater risk of memory or concentration problems!</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_20">• 4 times great risk of daytime fatigue or tiredness!</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_21">• 2 times great risk of falls and bone fractures (hip &amp; wrist)!</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_22">• 2 times great risk of having a motor vehicle accident!</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_23">RISK OF ALZHEIMER’S DISEASE:</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_24">Studies show that use of benzodiazepines is associated with greater risk of developing Alzheimer’s Disease:</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_25">• Click here for Article #1 </string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_26">• Click here for Article #2</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_27">FOR ALL OF THESE REASON’S, DR. STEWART DOES NOT RECOMMEND THESE MEDICATIONS FOR LONG-TERM, EVERY DAY USE.</string>
    <string name="benzodiazepine_28">In fact, Dr. Stewart suggests avoiding these medications all together.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_1">Low Back Pain is one of the most common reasons people go to see their doctor. The following is a “must see” video for all!</string>
    <string name="back_pain_2">* NOTE: in the second half of the video above, Dr. Evans explains why most people should <u>NOT</u> get an X-ray, CT scan or MRI for low back pain.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_3">ANOTHER WEBSITE:</string>
    <string name="back_pain_4">Check out BACK CARE CANADA to learn even more about back pain.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_5">IMPORTANT VIDEOS TO WATCH:</string>
    <string name="back_pain_6">If back pain has been a major problem for you, Dr. Stewart strongly recommends that you also watch the following video series by Dr. Hamilton Hall: </string>
    <string name="back_pain_7">WHAT YOU CAN DO FOR PAIN CONTROL:</string>
    <string name="back_pain_8">Strongly consider PHYSIOTHERAPY for severe, persisting, or recurrent back pain.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_9">REASONS TO SEE A DOCTOR (The “Red Flags”):</string>
    <string name="back_pain_10">• If your pain started with a big fall or accident and you fear a bone may be broken.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_11">• New trouble urinating (since your back pain started).</string>
    <string name="back_pain_12">• New leakage or incontinence of bowels (since your back pain started).</string>
    <string name="back_pain_13">• Numbness around your groin or genitals.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_14">• Weakness in your legs (NOTE: this refers to a true decrease in power, not just “weakness because of the pain).</string>
    <string name="back_pain_15">• Persisting fever with back pain.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_16">• History of IV drug use.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_17">• Unexplained weight loss.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_18">• Drenching night sweats (bad enough you have to change your clothing).</string>
    <string name="back_pain_19">• History of cancer (prostate, breast, or lung) and</string>
    <string name="back_pain_20">• Your pain is constant over many weeks or months, even during the night or with rest.</string>
    <string name="back_pain_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BOjTegn9RuY" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_1">What is Colon Cancer?</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_2">Colon cancer starts as a small “polyp” (like a skin-tag) inside a person’s colon wall. Over time, the polyp can grow into a colon cancer. This is a slow process. It can take many years to develop. We generally screen for polyps and colon cancer between the ages of 50 to 74 because that is when most people tend to develop them.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_3">There are two main ways to screen for colon cancer:</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_4">(i) A Fecal Occult Blood Test</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_5">(ii) A Colonoscopy</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_6">Fecal Occult Blood Test (FOBT): </string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_7">This is a take-home stool test that you can do in privacy of your own home. It tests for microscopic blood in your bowel movement (blood you cannot even see with your eyes). If there is an early cancer in your colon, it may be shedding off tiny amounts of blood, and this test can help detect it and prompt further investigation (by getting a colonoscopy). This is a quick, easy, and painless test.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_8">There are some problems with this FOBT test, though. It is not as accurate as a colonoscopy. It can miss about 30% (one third) of colon cancers. (However, if you do the test every year or two, the accuracy is better and it picks up most of the early cancers). The FOBT is also not good at picking up the polyps (the early start of a colon cancer) because polyps often do not shed blood.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_9">Another problem with the FOBT is that it cannot distinguish the source of the bleeding. For example, a bleeding hemorrhoid or even a bleeding stomach ulcer can cause the test to come back positive for blood.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_10">Colonoscopy:</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_11">You may know of friends or family who have had colonoscopies. Basically, you take a strong laxative the day before the procedure to totally clean out your bowel. You then go into the hospital for the procedure (but you are in and out the same day). They give you medications to doze you off, so you do not remember or feel anything, and then they go up inside your bottom end with a scope (which is basically a small video camera on the end of thin a flexible hose). From there, the doctor can directly see inside your colon wall and can see if there are any cancers or polyps. If they see a polyp, they can remove it right then and there before it ever turns into a cancer.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_12">The colonoscopy is a better test in that the doctor can actually directly see inside your colon. It is much more accurate. However, it is much more invasive and it does carry a very tiny risk of complication of popping through the bowel wall and requiring an operation to fix it (about 1 in 1000 to 1 in 10,000).</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_13">WHAT TEST SHOULD YOU GET?</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_14">If you have a direct family history (parents, siblings, or children) of colon cancer or even polyps, then you should get a colonoscopy. Remember to ask your family if they have had colonoscopies, what were the results? Even if it was “normal”, did they have any polyps? If so, you will need a colonoscopy as well.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_15">If you do not have a family history, then there is really no correct answer. Each test has its pros and cons, and it is whichever you prefer.</string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_16"><b>To get an FOBT, simply stop by our office and pick one up!</b></string>
    <string name="colon_cancer_screening_17"><b>To book a colonoscopy, call our office and ask for a referral. Your doctor may need you to come in for a visit to discuss this first, though.</b></string>
    <string name="concussions_1">Concussions are an injury to the brain. A concussion causes temporary changes in brain function that can affect thinking, vision, balance, and alertness. People with concussions usually have a headache. They may also feel confused, dazed, nausea, fuzzy vision, dizzy, or short term memory loss. Other symptoms include fatigue, trouble concentrating, and being irritable.</string>
    <string name="concussions_2">Most people with mild concussions recover quickly. However, concussions need to be take seriously.</string>
    <string name="concussions_3">Here is an excellent 10-minute video on concussions:</string>
    <string name="concussions_4">CARING FOR A CONCUSSION AT HOME:</string>
    <string name="concussions_5">• Watch closely in the first 24-48 hours for concerning symptoms (such as worsening headache, dizziness, drowsiness, fussiness, or irritability.</string>
    <string name="concussions_6">• Check the person at least once during the first night sleep to make sure he/she easily wakes up and is acting normally.</string>
    <string name="concussions_7">• Allow plenty of rest (“brain rest”).</string>
    <string name="concussions_8">• Allow gradual return to activities as discussed with your doctor (and as also shown in the video above). Go slow and do not rush recovery!</string>
    <string name="concussions_9">WHEN TO SEE A DOCTOR:</string>
    <string name="concussions_10">• a child who won’t stop crying or cannot be comforted.</string>
    <string name="concussions_11">• a headache that keeps getting worse.</string>
    <string name="concussions_12">• weakness or numbness in any part of the body.</string>
    <string name="concussions_13">• coordination or balance the gets worse.</string>
    <string name="concussions_14">• vomiting more than once after the head injury.</string>
    <string name="concussions_15">• slurred speech.</string>
    <string name="concussions_16">• cannot be awakened from sleep.</string>
    <string name="concussions_17">• increased confusion, irritability, or anxiety.</string>
    <string name="concussions_18">• has <i>any</i> symptom that seems to be getting worse.</string>
    <string name="concussions_vid"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_55YmblG9YM" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_1">People often suffer from infections that cause symptoms such as cough, runny nose, sinus congestion, sore throat, ear discomfort, and even mild fever or chills.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_2">These infections are usually caused by a virus.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_3">Most of the time, even people who think they have “Strep Throat” actually have a viral throat infection.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_4"><b>The bad news:</b> antibiotics do not work on viruses.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_5"><b>The good news:</b> Your body will fight off the virus on its own, usually within 5-10 days.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_6">DID YOU KNOW?  Coughs, colds &amp; sore throats last longer than most people think. Most to the time, you will be sick for at least 10 days.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_7">Here is Dr. Stewart’s Video to learn more:</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_8">Here is another excellent video you should watch:</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_9">WHAT ARE THE POTENTIAL HARMS OF ANTIBIOTICS?</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_10">• diarrhea, vomitting, and upset stomach</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_11">• rashes</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_12">• more severe allergic reactions</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_13">• resistance to antibiotics in future infections when they might really be needed.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_14">We understand that you are sick and want to feel better! Unfortunately, in most cases, there is nothing a doctor can prescribe you that will get you better any faster.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_15">Most of the time, you do not need to see a doctor. Your body simply needs time to fight off the infection. In the mean time, there are some things you can do to make yourself feel better.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_16">WHAT YOU CAN DO TO FEEL BETTER:</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_17">• Get lots of rest and drink plenty of fluids.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_18">• Studies show that <b>Echinacea</b> can reduce symptoms, if taken at the onset of the cold symptoms, and that <b>Vitamin C</b> can prevent the common cold.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_19">• Throat sprays, such as <b>Cepacol</b>, are very good at relieving sore throats. You can simply re-spray as needed.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_20">• <b>Nasal Saline flushes</b> or <b>Neti Pots</b> are very good at relieving nasal congestion and sinus discomfort.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_21">• Studies show that <b>Vicks VapoRub</b> can reduce cough &amp; cold symptoms. Some people even find it helpful to run over their sinus areas.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_22">• <i>All of these treatments are available over-the-counter from the pharmacy. You do not need to see your doctor for a prescription. You can also ask your local pharmacist for other useful products.</i></string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_23">REASONS TO SEE A DOCTOR:</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_24">• Severe or persistent fever.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_25">• If you have trouble breathing – especially if you are a smoker, have chronic bronchitis, emphysema, COPD, asthma, or other lung problems.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_26">• If your symptoms are getting <u>worse</u> after 7 days.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_27">• If you <i>just</i> a very sore throat and fever, but no stuffy nose and <i>no</i> cough (this may be a true “Strep throat).”</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_28">• If your sore throat is much worse on one side, or if you have trouble opening your jaw, or turning your neck.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_29">• If you are very unwell, or have any other concerning symptoms.</string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MD6fsg3hH-M" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="coughs_colds_and_sore_throats_vid_2"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vTC0JUoglB8" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="depression_1">Mental health conditions such as depression and anxiety are overwhelmingly common. Fortunately, there are a number of things you can do to help yourself feel better.</string>
    <string name="depression_2">• Counselling</string>
    <string name="depression_3">• Relaxation &amp; Stress Tips</string>
    <string name="depression_4">• Help with Financial Strain or Legal Issues</string>
    <string name="depression_5">• Lifestyle Changes (i.e. exercise, sleep, eating healthy)</string>
    <string name="depression_6">• Substance Use and Addictions Help</string>
    <string name="depression_7">• Medications for depression and/or anxiety</string>
    <string name="depression_8">• Brief CBT Techniques</string>
    <string name="diabetes_1">WHAT IS DIABETES?</string>
    <string name="diabetes_2">Here is an excellent, short, simple video that explains diabetes:</string>
    <string name="diabetes_3">Here is a brief video by Dr. Mike Evans on the “ABCs” of Diabetes:</string>
    <string name="diabetes_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MGL6km1NBWE" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="diabetes_vid_2"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MUb0nywugug" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="diarrhea_1">Diarrhea can either be new onset (“acute diarrhea”), or it could be a problem you have had recurrently for a long time (chronic diarrhea). This page is going to talk about the new onset type – in other words, the type of diarrhea people get when they get sick with a bug of some sort.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_2">“Acute Diarrhea” means diarrhea that has just started, sometimes abruptly, and it only lasts less than 2 weeks.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_3">WHAT CAUSES ACUTE DIARRHEA?</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_4">The most common cause of new diarrhea is an infection. The most common cause for that infection is VIRUS. It is often associated with nausea, vomitting, and belly cramps. This type of infection usually just has to ‘run it’s course’ and let your body fight it off. It usually lasts 3-7 days, although may last up to two weeks in some cases.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_5">Unfortunately, there is no special medication you can take to clear the virus faster. Antibiotics do not work on viruses, and in fact, they may only make the diarrhea worse!</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_6">***   MOST OF THE TIME, YOU DO NOT NEED TO SEE A DOCTOR FOR DIARRHEA.  IN FACT, YOU SHOULD USUALLY STAY HOME TO REST AND AVOID SPREADING THE GERMS TO OTHERS   ***</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_7">In rare cases, the diarrhea can be caused by a BACTERIA, but that is usually associated with certain risk factors, which will be shown below.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_8">WHAT CAN YOU DO FOR THE DIARRHEA?</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_9">Your body just needs time to fight off the virus. In the mean time, here are some things you can do:</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_10">• Drink plenty of fluids to prevent yourself from becoming dehydrated from all the fluids you are losing from diarrhea and/or vomitting.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_11">• If you do not have any of the “reasons to see a doctor” listed below, then you can take over-the-counter Imodium. This slows down your bowel so that you don’t have as much diarrhea. (Be careful not to take too much, though, or you can actually constipate yourself!)</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_12">THE REASONS YOU MAY NEED TO SEE A DOCTOR</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_13">• Recently taken antibiotics.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_14">• Recently travelled outside of North America.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_15">• Recently been hospitalized.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_16">• May have eaten spoiled foods or water.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_17">• Recent camping and drank water from the outdoors.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_18">REASONS TO DEFINITELY SEE YOUR DOCTOR</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_19">• Severe, watery diarrhea with signs of dehydration – such as, dry mouth and tongue, thirst, muscle cramps, very dark-colored urine, urinating infrequently, and dizziness or lightheadedness after sitting up.  (Note: if you are having these symptoms, you may need to go directly to ER for IV fluids instead of seeing your family doctor).</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_20">• Severe belly pains.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_21">• A fever that is very high or lasts longer than a day or two.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_22">• Blood in the diarrhea or stool.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_23">• If it lasts longer than 2 weeks.</string>
    <string name="diarrhea_24">• If you seem have recurrent diarrhea quite frequently over time.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_1">WHAT IS A MIDDLE EAR INFECTION?</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_2">Middle ear infection is an infection in the small space just inside the eardrum that is common in young children. It is also called otitis media and usually causes an earache.  The medical term for this type of ear infection is called, “Acute Otitis Media”.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_3">(There is a different type of ear infection called an “Outer Ear Infection” (a.k.a. “Swimmer’s Ear”) that is totally different).</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_4">Click HERE for more information on Outer Ear Infections.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_5">Most children will have at least one middle ear infection by 3 years of age.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_6">Middle ear infections are more common in winter and early spring and often come with cold symptoms and even a fever.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_7">WILL ANTIBIOTICS HELP RIGHT NOW?</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_8">Middle ear infections are usually caused by a virus, but sometimes can be caused by a bacteria. Most children (80\%%) recover from the pain on their own within 1-2 days without antibiotics!</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_9">Your child’s own immune system will be able to get rid of the infection in a few days in most cases.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_10">Research shows that antibiotics do NOT relieve earache in the first 24 hours. In fact, only 1 in 20 children treated with antibiotics are actually helped by taking antibiotics. (i.e. for 95\%% of children antibiotics do not help!). (HOWEVER, 1 in 8 children who take antibiotics experience side effects or reactions from them!)</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_11">WHAT ARE THE POTENTIAL HARMS OF ANTIBIOTICS?</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_12">• diarrhea and vomitting</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_13">• rashes</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_14">• more severe allergic reactions</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_15">• resistance to antibiotics in future infections when they might really be needed.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_16">WHAT CAN YOU DO TO MAKE YOUR CHILD FEEL BETTER?</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_17">WHEN SHOULD YOUR CHILD SEE A DOCTOR?</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_18">• If your child is not starting to get better in 2-3 days.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_19">• Fever that will not go down even with Tylenol and Advil.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_20">• Swelling or redness behind the ear.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_21">• If you are worried your child is in any way seriously ill.</string>
    <string name="ear_infections_22">• If your child gets frequent ear infections each year and/or you are worried about your child’s speech and language development.</string>
    <string name="fever_1">Fever in Children</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_1">** Here are 7 Simple Questions to help people living with money troubles. **</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_2">** Click the link to see if any apply to you **</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_3">Ontario Works (a.k.a. “Social Services)</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_4">Financial assistance and employment supports including training and skills development, academic upgrading, and work placements. Click on their website link or call them at 613-473-5258. Their address is 56 Russell Street North in Madoc.</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_5">Hastings County Social Housing – Provides safe, modest and affordable housing for low income households.</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_6">Contact the Intake Access Centre at 613-771-9630 or 1-866-414-0300 during regular business hours Monday-Friday from 8:30am-4:30pm. Staff will help you complete an application over the phone. You must have a valid Social Insurance Number to apply. You may also apply online.</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_7">Central Hastings Support Network </string>
    <string name="financial_strain_8">The Central Hastings Support Network (CHSN) is a registered, non-profit Corporation that delivers programs for the benefit of the Central Hastings community. Programs are developed and delivered to meet the needs of people suffering from the lack of adequate resources, poverty, age, disability or other vulnerability. Click their website link, email them at supportnetwork@chsninc.ca, or call them at 613-473-5255. Their address is 151 St. Lawrence Avenue East in Madoc.</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_9">Community Advocacy &amp; Legal Centre (CALC)</string>
    <string name="financial_strain_10">The Community Advocacy &amp; Legal Centre provides access to justice through quality legal services, help and information for people living on a low income or in poverty. Click on their website link or call them at 613-966-8686. Their address in Madoc is 151 St. Lawrence Street East, Suite 5.</string>
    <string name="headaches_1">Headache Prevention</string>
    <string name="headaches_2">For people suffer from frequent headaches, preventing headaches is even more important treating a headache once once occurs. Here are some important tips to prevent headaches. Some of the tips may sound simple, but please do not underestimate how effective they can be.</string>
    <string name="headaches_3">HOW TO PREVENT HEADACHES</string>
    <string name="headaches_4">• <b>Proper Sleep:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_5">  – Get enough sleep at night.</string>
    <string name="headaches_6">  – No napping during the day.</string>
    <string name="headaches_7">  – Try to wake up the same time every day. Do not sleep in on weekends.</string>
    <string name="headaches_8">• <b>Water:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_9">  – Drink at least 1.5 liters per day (i.e. three 500ml bottles or 6 cups)</string>
    <string name="headaches_10">  – Avoid drinks with added sugars or artificial colours</string>
    <string name="headaches_11">• <b>Avoid Caffeine:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_12">  – Caffeine can cause headaches.</string>
    <string name="headaches_13">• <b>Exercise:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_14">  – Exercise daily, even just a 30 minute walk.</string>
    <string name="headaches_15">  – If you cannot go outside, try walking around inside your house.</string>
    <string name="headaches_16">• <b>Eat Regulary:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_17">  – Eat a healthy and balanced diet eat regular times through the day.</string>
    <string name="headaches_18">• <b>Avoid Too Much Medications:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_19">  – Sometimes taking over-the-counter medications like Tylenol and Advil can cause a headache if taken too often. (i.e. taking as little as 2 days per week or 5 days per month).</string>
    <string name="headaches_20">  – Especially avoid medications with caffeine or codeine (like Tylenol #1).</string>
    <string name="headaches_21">• <b>Natural/Herbal Remedies:</b></string>
    <string name="headaches_22">  – These natural remedies are recommended by headache specialists. They can be just as effective as prescription medications at preventing headaches. <i>Try taking one of the following DAILY prevent headaches:</i></string>
    <string name="headaches_23">  – Butterbur 50mg two or three times per day</string>
    <string name="headaches_24">  – CoEnzyme Q10 100mg three times per day</string>
    <string name="headaches_25">  – Magnesium 300mg to 600mg daily</string>
    <string name="headaches_26">  – Riboflavin 400mg daily</string>
    <string name="liver_1">Fatty Liver</string>
    <string name="liver_2">WHAT DOES YOUR LIVER DO?</string>
    <string name="liver_3">WHAT IS “FATTY LIVER”?</string>
    <string name="liver_4">Fatty Liver refers to a condition where fat cells are deposited in your liver. The fat cells come from things like your diet, alcohol, and cholesterol. If you get too much fat in your liver, it can be harmful. It can cause damage by scarring, inflammation, and cirrhosis.</string>
    <string name="liver_5">Most of the time, you will not have any symptoms from a fatty liver.  Symptoms do not appear until your liver is very damaged (in the later stages of fatty liver disease).</string>
    <string name="liver_6">Your doctor may discover signs of fatty liver through routine blood tests. Sometimes, fatty liver is found by accident (“coincidentally”) by an ultrasound of your belly that was ordered for some other reason.</string>
    <string name="liver_7">ALCOHOL:</string>
    <string name="liver_8">Drinking too much alcohol is common cause for having a fatty liver. If you drink more than the following, it can be harmful for your health:</string>
    <string name="liver_9">• 14 drinks per week for males</string>
    <string name="liver_10">• 7 drinks per week for females</string>
    <string name="liver_11">7 drinks per week for females</string>
    <string name="liver_12">NON-ALCOHOLIC FATTY LIVER DISEASE:</string>
    <string name="liver_13">People can have fatty liver disease for reasons other than alcohol. This is called “Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease” (NAFLD). This is becoming a very common disease in North America due to increased rates of obesity, diabetes, poor diet, and lack of exercise.</string>
    <string name="liver_14">For even more information on Fatty Liver Disease, be sure to visit the:</string>
    <string name="liver_15">Canadian Liver Foundation’s website.</string>
    <string name="liver_16">HOW DO YOU TREAT OR PREVENT FATTY LIVER DISEASE?</string>
    <string name="liver_17">There are not many proven ways to treat fatty liver disease. The main treatments are simple, but sometimes hard for people:</string>
    <string name="liver_18">• Try to <b>stop drinking alcohol</b>, or at least cut back to the recommended amounts shown above.</string>
    <string name="liver_19">• Besides limiting alcohol, <b>LOSING WEIGHT</b> is the absolute best way to treat fatty liver disease.</string>
    <string name="liver_20">• Eat a balanced and <b>healthy diet</b>.</string>
    <string name="liver_21">• <b>Exercise</b> and maintain an active lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="liver_22">• Some research has shown that taking Vitamin E (800 units per day) can help. <b>Vitamin E</b> can be purchased “over-the-counter” and is not a prescription medication.</string>
    <string name="liver_23">WHAT IS “FATTY LIVER”?</string>
    <string name="liver_24">If you have been told you have fatty liver disease, you should try to drink even less than that. Ideally, you should drink as little alcohol as possible.</string>
    <string name="liver_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O71niTozP-o" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="metamucil_1">Metamucil is a natural fiber that can cure many bowel problems, including both constipation and diarrhea! It also has other health benefits such as lowering psylliumcholesterol and risk of colon cancer.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_2">WHAT IS METAMUCIL?</string>
    <string name="metamucil_3">Metamucil contains a special type of fiber called “psyllium”. Metamucil is the brand name of the product. You may also find generic brands of psyllium that are less expensive, but you may find that the brand name Metamucil works better for you.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_4">Psyllium is a source of both soluble and insoluble fibre. Soluble fibre helps to soften stools. It will either form a gel-like material when added to water (such as psyllium fibre found Metamucil) or it will dissolve completely in water. Insoluble fibre does not dissolve in water. It moves through your digestive system largely intact so it helps to bulk up stools. Both kinds are important</string>
    <string name="metamucil_5">HOW DOES IT WORK?</string>
    <string name="metamucil_6">The fiber works as a sponge. It absorbs the extra water and adds bulk to the stool. Think of your bowel as a tube of toothpaste: When there is not much toothpaste left in the tube, it is hard to squeeze out the toothpaste. However, when there is a lot of bulk and the tube is full, it is very easy to squeeze out the toothpaste.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_7">If your stool is too hard, that same sponge-like fiber absorbs water up into the stool and softens it.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_8">For these reasons, Metacucil can cure both constipation and diarrhea. It is like a miracle cure for all!</string>
    <string name="metamucil_9">DON’T FORGET TO ADD WATER!</string>
    <string name="metamucil_10">When taking Metamucil, you will need to remember to drink more fluids during the day as well. If you add too much fiber and bulk without adding enough water, this can make constipation worse.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_11">Men may need to take in 10 cups of fluid per day. Woman may need to aim for 8 cups. (1 cup = 250ml)</string>
    <string name="metamucil_12">HOW DO YOU TAKE METAMUCIL?</string>
    <string name="metamucil_13">The most common form of Metamucil comes in a powder. You mix it in water and drink it. Metamucil also comes in a pill (capsule) form. The powder form is less expensive. For some people, the pill form is more convenient, but be prepared to be taking at least 6 to 12 (or more!) of the pills per day.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_14">There is no “correct” dose of Metamucil to take. Everyone may need a different amount per day for desired effect. The trick is to start with a low dose, like 1 scoop per day (or 6 pills per day). Try this for 3 or 4 days in a row and see how things go. After 3 or 4 days at the low dose, if you are not having success with your bowel movements, then try increasing the dose a little higher, like to 1 scoop TWICE per day (or 6 pills TWICE per day). Then see how things go after 3 or 4 days more on that dose. You may have to adjust your dose further from there.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_15">Again, everyone’s body is different and everyone will need a different amount for desired effect. Just keep adjusting your dose a little up (or down) every 3 to 4 days until you find the right amount that works for you.</string>
    <string name="metamucil_16">WHAT NOT TO BUY!</string>
    <string name="metamucil_17">Metamucil now comes in a different version that contains a fiber called INULIN, <u>instead of psyillium</u>. DO NOT BUY THE INULIN KIND. It causes people to have lots of gas and cramping.</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_1">WHAT IS OSTEOPOROSIS?</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_2">Osteoporosis is a disease where a person’s bones are weak and brittle. People with osteoporosis are at a high risk of breaking their bones, especially the hip, spine, wrist and shoulder.</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_3">Osteoporosis does not develop overnight. You can lose bone strength steadily for many years without experiencing any symptoms or signs of the disease until it is too late and a bone fractures. By that time, it is too late to turn back the clock, so prevention is key! (see below).</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_4">Note: <i>Osteoporosis is sometimes confused with “osteoarthritis”, because the names are sound similar. Osteoporosis is a disease of brittle bones, whereas osteoarthritis is the arthritis that causes pain from ‘wear on tear’ on a person’s joints</i>.</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_5">PREVENTION IS KEY!</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_6">Keeping your bones strong is important at any age, but it is very important after the age of 50. It is especially important to women after menopause, because that is when bones are at even greater risk of becoming weaker.</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_7">There are many things you can do to strengthen your bones and prevent them from becoming weaker:</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_8">• Limit alcohol intake (no more than 2 drinks per day for males and no more than 1 drink per day for females).</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_9">• Limit caffeine intake. Caffeine weakens bones too.</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_10">HOW DO WE TEST FOR OSTEOPOROSIS?</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_11">The strength of your bones can be detected by a “Bone Mineral Density” test. This is like a fancy x-ray of your hip and lower spine that tells us how dense your bones are. It does not hurt one bit!</string>
    <string name="osteoporosis_12">WHAT ABOUT PRESCRIPTION MEDICATIONS?</string>
    <string name="pain_1"><b>“Acute pain”</b> means the pain is new and is of short duration. It serves as a warning of injury to your body. Acute pain might be caused by many events, such as a surgery, a broken bone, a strained muscle, or a cut.</string>
    <string name="pain_2">CLICK HERE for more information.</string>
    <string name="pain_3"><b>“Chronic pain”</b> means pain that has lasted for a long time, longer than 3 months. It persists even though the initial injury has healed. There are many causes for chronic pain and some of them are very complicated. With chronic pain, it is important to remember that ‘hurt’ does not necessarily mean ‘harm’.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_1">WHAT IS PINK EYE?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_2">“Pink eye” is the everyday term people use to describe an infection or irritation of the eye. The medical term for pinkeye is “conjunctivitis.”</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_3">If you have pinkeye, your eye (or eyes) might:</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_4">● Turn red or pink</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_5">● Weep or ooze a gooey liquid</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_6">● Feel itchy, irritated, or mild burning</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_7">● Get stuck shut</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_8">WHAT CAUSES PINK EYE?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_9">Pinkeye can be caused by an infection, allergies, or an unknown irritation. The most common form of pink eye is caused by a VIRAL infection and is commonly associated with common cold symptoms.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_10">CAN YOU CATCH PINK EYE FROM SOMEONE ELSE?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_11">Yes. When pinkeye is caused by an infection, it can spread easily. Usually, people catch it from touching something that has touched an infected person’s eye.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_12">If you know someone with pinkeye, avoid touching his or her pillowcases, towels, or other personal items.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_13">WHEN SHOULD YOU SEE A DOCTOR?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_14"><b><i>Most of the time, the pink eye that people get that is associated with common cold symptoms does NOT need to be seen by a doctor. In fact, you should probably stay home to avoid spreading the germs.</i></b></string>
    <string name="pink_eye_15">Reasons to see a doctor:</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_16">• if you have pink eye that is not associated with cold symptoms.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_17">• if your eye is “painful” or “hurts”, as opposed to simply feeling irritated.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_18">• if your eye is sensitive to light.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_19">• if you notice changes in your vision (besides just mild blurriness from the extra tearing or mucous).</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_20">• if your eye is more red than pink and/or has A LOT of mucous or pus (as in the second picture here).</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_21">• if you have been wearing contact lenses along with having pink eye.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_22">• if things are not improving after a week.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_23">• if you have any other concerns that something may be more seriously wrong.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_24">CAN PINK EYE BE TREATED?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_25">When pink eye is caused by infection, it is usually caused by a VIRUS, so antibiotics or drops will NOT help.  (Antibiotics do not kill viruses; they only kill bacteria, which is a different type of germ). Pink eye caused by a virus will usually go away on its own in a few days, but may last even a week or more.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_26">You may consider using over-the-counter natural tear drops. These drops will not cure the pinkeye, but they can help with itchiness and irritation.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_27">When using eye drops for infection, do not touch your good eye after touching your affected eye, and do not touch the bottle or dropper directly in one eye and then use it in the other. Both of these things can cause the infection to spread from one eye to the other.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_28">WHAT IF I WEAR CONTACT LENSES?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_29">If you wear contact lenses and you have symptoms of pinkeye, it may be important to have a doctor look at your eyes. In people who wear contacts, the symptoms of pinkeye can be caused by serious problems.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_30">While you have pink eye, you should stop wearing your contacts for a short time. Plus, you might need to throw away your contact lens case and carefully clean your contacts. If your contacts are disposable, you will want to throw them away and start fresh.</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_31">CAN PINK EYE BE PREVENTED?</string>
    <string name="pink_eye_32">To keep from getting or spreading pinkeye, wash your hands often with soap and water. If washing is not possible, alcohol-based hand gels work, too. AVOID TOUCHING OR RUBBING YOUR EYES. Also, avoid sharing towels, bed clothes, or other personal items with a person who has pinkeye.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_1">The PSA test – The “Prostate Blood Test”</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_2">Many men wonder if they should get checked for prostate cancer with a blood test (the PSA blood test – “PSA = Prostate Specific Antigen”). This is a very complicated discussion. For most men, the PSA test is no longer recommended as a general screening test. However, if you have urinary symptoms or a family history of prostate cancer, the PSA test may be useful and you should check with your doctor to discuss this.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_3">ABOUT PROSTATE CANCER</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_4">Prostate cancer is very common. Up to 50\%% of men in their 50s will have a tiny prostate cancer brewing inside of them. 90% of 90-year-olds will have a prostate cancer inside them! HOWEVER, most of these prostate cancers are slow-growing and often do not cause any harm. As sad as it is to say, most of these men end up dying from other more common causes such heart attacks, strokes, or other cancers. The prostate cancer will never really harm most of these men.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_5">Studies show that, among men 55–69 who did not get screened with a PSA test, the risk of dying from prostate cancer after 13 years was 6 in 1,000. With regular PSA screening, the risk of dying from prostate cancer may be reduced to 5 in 1,000. That’s only 1 in 1000 lives saved, and 5 men still died despite getting screened!</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_6">THE HARMS OF PSA TESTING</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_7">You might ask, “Well, why not still do the PSA test in order to save 1 in 1000 lives?”  The answer is because doing the PSA test can cause potential harm to men.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_8">The PSA test is not a perfect test. It can come back high even when there is no actual prostate cancer. There are many other reasons that can cause a high PSA level besides cancer. If a man gets a PSA test that comes back high, that can cause anxiety and worry for that man. It can then lead to a number of other tests and specialist visits (including a prostate biopsy, which is quite painful and not without risk). Then, if the final results come back normal (NO prostate cancer), that man has just undergone all that needless worry, tests, and risks.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_9">WHAT IF THE PSA TEST ACTUALLY FINDS A CANCER, THOUGH?</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_10">If a high PSA test leads to a prostate biopsy and that biopsy actually confirms a cancer, then that leads to more things to consider.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="prostate_cancer_11">Having a surgery to remove the prostate cancer (a “prostatectomy”), carries up to a 45% chance risk the man will have trouble getting erections for the rest of his life (erectile dysfunction). It also carries up to a 20% risk the man will have long-term urinary incontinence afterwards. These are very significant risks for most men!</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_12"><u>HERE IS A VERY IMPORTANT POINT</u>: Knowing these risks, and knowing that most prostate cancers are slow-growing and may never affect them, many men will decide NOT to get their prostates removed. If that is the case, then why go looking for a prostate cancer in the first place!?  (There is no point in even doing the PSA test to look for cancer, and undergo all the worry and tests, if your final answer will be NOT to get your prostate removed anyway!)</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_13">SO WHAT SHOULD YOU DO?</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_14">As you can see, this is a very complicated decision. Before deciding on getting a PSA test, you should think about the pros and cons of doing so. For most men, the recommendation is not do a PSA test, but there may be special reasons you may wish to do so.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_15">HOWEVER, if you are having urinary symptoms, or have a family history of prostate cancer, you should see your doctor for further assessment and discussion.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_16">If you are 70 years of age or older, you should NOT get the PSA test. The risks of doing the test far outweigh the benefits.</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_17"><b>SEE BELOW FOR AN EXCELLENT VIDEO EXPLAINING ALL OF THIS IN MORE DETAIL:</b></string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_18">And here is short additional video that looks a little deeper at the PSA numbers:</string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bTgS0DuhaUU" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="prostate_cancer_vid_2"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-twQj6GwQBI" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_1">Shoulder pain is a very common reason for which people go to see a doctor. This page is meant to provide some information about the common shoulder pains that are caused by muscle or joint issues.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_2">Here is a short and detailed video of the anatomy of the shoulder:</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_3">COMMON CAUSES OF SHOULDER PAIN:</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_4">• A muscle tear (either partial or complete)</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_5">• A muscle strain</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_6">• Tendinitis</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_7">• Ligament strain</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_8">• Arthritis</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_9">• A “pinched nerve” in the neck</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_10">• <i>Regardless of the specific cause, the treatment is usually the same for all.</i></string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_11"><b>IMPORTANT NOTE:</b> Sometimes people can feel pain the shoulder that is actually red flag caused by serious heart or lung problems. If you are in doubt, see your doctor as soon as possible, even go to the Emergency Department if need be.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_12">WHAT CAN YOU DO TO IMPROVE YOUR PAIN?</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_13">• Rest. Avoid activities that aggravate the pain.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_14">• Ice.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_15">• Tylenol (click for more information)</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_16">• Anti-inflammatories, as long as they are safe for you to take. (click for more information).</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_17">• If your pain is persistent over several weeks, then other medications may be helpful, such as Cymbalta, Lyrica, gabapentin, amitiptyline, or nortriptyline. You may have to see your doctor for a prescription for these types of medications.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_18"><b>• But the #1 suggestion for persistent shoulder pain is PHYSIOTHERAPY</b></string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_19">• </string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_20">• </string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_21">• </string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_22">• </string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_23">DO YOU NEED AN XRAY, ULTRASOUND, OR MRI?</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_24">In the vast majority of cases, you do <u>NOT</u> require any of these imaging tests. This is because regardless of the cause, the <u>treatment is still the same</u> for all the different causes.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_25">Regardless of whether the cause is from a muscle tear, a strain, tendonitis, arthritis, or a pinched nerve, they all lead to the same treatment suggestions: rest, ice, pain medications, and PHYSIOTHERAPY.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_26">Even if you have a rotator cuff tear, most of the time the orthopaedic surgeons recommend a trial 4-6 weeks of physiotherapy before they would even consider offering a surgery.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_27">Furthermore, physiotherapists are “muscle and joint experts”. They can thoroughly assess you and often figure out what is wrong, even without imaging tests.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_28">The main times when an X-ray or ultrasound are required may be if there was a sudden injury to your shoulder. In these cases, it may be important to rule out broken bones, dislocations, or muscles that have suddenly become torn.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_29">REASONS TO SEE YOUR DOCTOR:</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_30">• You are concerned your pain could be from something more serious, like a heart or lung problem, as noted above.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_31">• Your pain is lasting more than 4-6 weeks, despite trying the above recommended treatments.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_32">• Your pain is caused from a sudden injury or fall, and you are worried that something may be broken or dislocated.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_33">• If your shoulder is red or significantly bruised.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_34">• Your pain is severe and not controlled by the above treatments.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_pain_35">• You are concerned that something else is wrong, or have any other questions or concerns.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_1">Patients often see their family doctor to look at a worrisome skin spot or “mole.” Many types of skin spots are not worrisome and do not require any treatment. However, sometimes skin spots do need to be assessed and treated. This page will give you more information about some of the skin spots that you should know about.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_2">MELANOMA:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_3">By far the more worrisome type of skin cancer is a “melanoma.” These are rare, but they are extremely dangerous.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_4">Melanomas are often very dark or black in colour. They appear irregular in shape. They can start as an odd looking mole and quickly progress.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_5">** CLICK HERE FOR MORE INFORMATION ON HOW TO RECOGNIZE A MELANOMA, INCLUDING A EXCELLENT VIDEO **</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_6">See your doctor as soon as possible if you think you may have a melanoma!</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_7">Here some pictures of melanomas to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_8">SQUAMOUS CELL CANCERS:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_9">This is a different type of skin cancer. They are less urgent than melanomas, but they still need to be assessed by a doctor and treated.  They usually occur in sun-exposed areas of the body, like the head, face, lips, neck, back, arms, or hands. They come in all shapes and sizes. They often look red or pink. They often appear scabbed or raw.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_10">See your doctor if you think you have a Squamous Cell Cancer.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_11">Here some pictures of Squamous Cell Cancers to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_12">BASAL CELL CANCERS:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_13">This type is skin cancer is the most common. It is generally not worrisome, but you still need to see your doctor or it will just continue to grow and grow. The larger it becomes, the more difficult it becomes to get rid of.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_14">Basal Cell Cancers often look like open sores, red patches, pink growths, or shiny bumps. They often have an “erosive” or “dented” surface.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_15">It is not urgent, but still see your doctor if you think you have a Basal Cell Cancer.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_16">Here are some pictures of Basal Cell Cancers to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_17">SOLAR KERATOSIS (aka “Actinic Keratosis”):</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_18">These are very common to see on sun-exposed areas, like the face, scalp, arms, and hands. They often start as small, mildly red or pink spots that feel rough when you run your fingers over them. They can progress to become larger, more red, and with thick crusts on the surface. People often find that the crusts keep falling off, but then keep coming back, and the spot never heals.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_19">Solar Keratosis are easily treated in your family doctor’s office with liquid nitrogen. They are not urgent, but if left untreated they can turn into a squamous cell cancer (see above for more information on squamous cell cancers).</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_20">It is not urgent, but still see your doctor if you think you have a Solar Keratosis.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_21">Here are some pictures of Solar Keratosis to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_22">SEBORRHEIC KERATOSIS (aka “Seb K’s):</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_23">People often come to the doctor asking about these spots. They are extremely common and can occur anywhere on the body. Seb K’s usually appears as a brown, black or light tan growth. The growth has a waxy, scaly, slightly elevated appearance. They almost appear “stuck on” to the skin.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_24"><b>Although these spots look unusual, they are totally benign. You do <u>not</u> need to see your doctor for these spots</b> (unless the spot has unusual features in it that may resemble one of the skin cancers above). </string>
    <string name="skin_spots_25">Here are some pictures of Seb K’s to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_26">SKIN TAGS:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_27">These are harmless, soft growths or “tags”. They tend to occur in areas of friction, such as in armpits, neck, or groin.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_28">Skin tags are totally benign. You do not need to see your doctor for these.</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_29">Here are some pictures of skin tags to help you recognize them:</string>
    <string name="skin_spots_30">** The above is simply a general guide to some of skin spots that you should know about. If you are concerned about a skin spot, please see your doctor for a proper assessment. **</string>
    <string name="sleep_1">Sleep &amp; Insomnia</string>
    <string name="sleep_2">EVERYONE has trouble sleeping at some time or another, even for weeks or months at a time.</string>
    <string name="sleep_3">YES, you may be tired the next day after a poor night’s sleep, but it’s not the end of the world. People make a “catastrophe” out of getting a poor night’s sleep, but it’s really not.</string>
    <string name="sleep_4">Sleep medications should only be used as sparingly as possible, maybe two times per week at most. They should NOT be taken every night.</string>
    <string name="sleep_5">DR. STEWART’S SLEEP MEDICINE PRESCRIPTIONS:</string>
    <string name="sleep_6">• Dr. Stewart will not prescribe more than 5 doses per week.</string>
    <string name="sleep_7">• This ensures patients do not to rely on pills every single night to sleep. It allows  their bodies to remember how to fall asleep naturally.</string>
    <string name="sleep_8">• Even someone who works 5 days per week should not require sleeping medications during weekends.</string>
    <string name="sleep_9">• If you are retired or not employed, there should be even less need for sleep medications because you do not have to worry about being tired for work the next day!</string>
    <string name="sleep_10">INSTEAD OF MEDICATIONS, TRY THE FOLLOWING …</string>
    <string name="sleep_11">Sleep Hygiene:</string>
    <string name="sleep_12">• Avoid Caffeine. For some people, caffeine stays in their bodies for up to 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="sleep_13">• Avoid alcohol. Alcohol causes drowsiness, but it actually keeps you from being able to sleep properly through the night.</string>
    <string name="sleep_14">• Quit smoking. Cigarettes and nicotine are stimulants. They significantly interfere with sleep.</string>
    <string name="sleep_15">• Avoid heavy meals or too much liquid before bedtime.</string>
    <string name="sleep_16">• Get regular exercise during the day, but avoid heavy exercise within 3 hours of bedtime.</string>
    <string name="sleep_17">• Keep your bedroom quiet, dark, and comfortable temperature. Minimize noise and light. Some people need total darkness to sleep. However, a quiet background fan or “white noise” may be helpful.</string>
    <string name="sleep_18">• Avoid watching or checking the clock. Stop obsessing about your sleep.</string>
    <string name="sleep_19">• </string>
    <string name="sleep_20">• Avoid napping during the day.</string>
    <string name="sleep_21">• Keep a routine. Try to go to bed and wake up ever day around the same time, even on weekends.</string>
    <string name="sleep_22">Stimulus Control:</string>
    <string name="sleep_23">• Remove the TV and computer from the bedroom.</string>
    <string name="sleep_24">• Avoid watching TV or using a computer or tablet before bed. They use bright, stimulating lights that make it difficult to fall asleep after.</string>
    <string name="sleep_25">• Go to bed only when you feel tired, even if later than you planned.</string>
    <string name="sleep_26">• Get out of bed if not able to sleep within 20 minutes. Go to another room and relax. Try a relaxing activity, such as reading. Avoid watching TV or the computer. Return to bed only when sleepy.</string>
    <string name="sleep_27">Relations Strategies:</string>
    <string name="sleep_28">• Avoid arousing activities before bed (i.e. late night phone calls, doing work, watching TV).</string>
    <string name="sleep_29">• Designate at least 1 hour before bedtime to help unwind from the day’s stresses. You can even trying dimming the lights.</string>
    <string name="sleep_30">• Do something relaxing before bed such as reading, deep breathing, stretching, yoga, or relaxation CDs.</string>
    <string name="sleep_31">Books &amp; Self-help:</string>
    <string name="sleep_32">• Go to your local bookstore or online and check out the many options to learn more about insomnia and self-manage your sleep.</string>
    <string name="sleep_33">• For example, “The Insomnia Workbook” by Stephanie Silberman and Charles Morin insomnia is an excellent book.</string>
    <string name="sleep_34">• If you have a smartphone, there are many apps available for insomnia and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="sleep_35">5 KEY QUESTIONS on Insomnia: </string>
    <string name="sleep_36">** Be Sure to also check out Dr. Mike Evans’ handout on sleep. Click Here for more information and resources. **</string>
    <string name="sleep_37">SLEEP CONSOLIDATION:</string>
    <string name="sleep_38">OTHER FACTORS THAT CAN CAUSE TROUBLE SLEEPING:</string>
    <string name="sleep_39">Some people may have medical conditions that cause poor sleep, such as:</string>
    <string name="sleep_40">• Obstructive Sleep Apnea (associated with loud snoring).</string>
    <string name="sleep_41">• Urinary or Prostate Problems (causing frequent urination during the night).</string>
    <string name="sleep_42">• Mood Disorders (such as anxiety or depression).</string>
    <string name="sleep_43">• Asthma or COPD (chronic bronchitis or emphysema).</string>
    <string name="sleep_44">• Chronic Pain.</string>
    <string name="sleep_45">• Heartburn or Gastric Reflux (“GERD”).</string>
    <string name="sleep_46">• Restless Leg Syndrome.</string>
    <string name="sleep_47">• Side effects of other medications.</string>
    <string name="sleep_48">Speak to your doctor if you think any of these other conditions are affecting your sleep.</string>
    <string name="smoking_1">If you smoke cigarettes, quitting smoking is probably the #1 BEST THING you can do for your health.  (It is also one of the most difficult).</string>
    <string name="smoking_2">Here is a great video by Dr. Mike Evans on quitting smoking. If you smoke, please take the 12 minutes to watch it. It’s worth it!!</string>
    <string name="smoking_3">NEED HELP?</string>
    <string name="smoking_4">WHAT ABOUT MEDICATIONS TO HELP?</string>
    <string name="smoking_5">Some people prefer to try to quit “cold turkey”, but that approach may not work for everyone. People often need additional help.</string>
    <string name="smoking_6">Before turning to prescription medications, it is now recommended that you try some form of Nicotine Replacement Therapy to help reduce the cravings that occur when a person tries to quit smoking.</string>
    <string name="smoking_7">There are many different types of Nicotine Replacement Therapy: patches, gums, nasal sprays, inhalers, or lozenges. All of these are available over-the-counter, without prescription, from your local pharmacy. Ask your pharmacist for advice on how to use these products.</string>
    <string name="smoking_8">Prescription medications to help quit smoking may not be for everyone, but if you are interested these, contact your doctor to discuss.</string>
    <string name="smoking_9">A BOOK THAT SOME PEOPLE HAVE FOUND HELPFUL:</string>
    <string name="smoking_10">There is a famous book, written by Allen Carr, that has worked very well for some people. The book is a little unconventional, but it may really be helpful for people who feel they are not even ready to quit. It may help some people think about smoking in a different way.  The book is called “Easy Way to Stop Smoking“. There are even audiobook versions, or copies to loan from your local library.</string>
    <string name="smoking_vid_1"><![CDATA[<html><body><iframe width="%1$f" height="%2$f" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z16vhtjWKL0" frameborder="0" </iframe></body></html>]]></string>
    <string name="stroke_1">Here is an excellent 5-minute video about Strokes by HealthSketch:</string>
    <string name="stroke_2">IMPORTANT:</string>
    <string name="stroke_3">• if you ever have symptoms of a stroke, call the ambulance (911) and/or have someone drive you to the the nearest Emergency Department <u>immediately.</u></string>
    <string name="stroke_4">• Do NOT waste valuable time by waiting to see your family doctor’s office.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_1">Obesity is a huge problem (pun intended). Over half of Canadians are obese or overweight. Being overweight contributes to many (nearly all?) health problems – both physically and mentally! Obesity severely impacts a person’s quality of life.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_2">There are thousands of different websites and resources on the internet with information on how to lose weight- some good, some misleading, and some with even terrible advice. The purpose of this webpage is to provide a <u>simple</u>, <u>basic</u>, approach to losing weight.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_3">THE BASICS OF WEIGHT LOSS:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_4">Weight loss (and weight gain) are the result of unequal balance of energy. “Energy” is measured as “calories”.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_5">BASIC POINTS:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_6">• <b>To lose weight, you must burn more energy (calories) than you eat in a day.</b></string>
    <string name="weight_loss_7">• The opposite is also true. If you eat more calories than you burn in a day, then you will gain weight.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_8">• You burn calories OUT by two ways:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_9">• Just to live your body uses energy to breath, to make your heart beat, and to digest food. You are even burning small amounts of energy to do these things while you sleep. This is called your Basal Metabolic Rate (aka “BMR”).</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_10">• You burn additional calories through day by physical activity. This includes formal exercise, but it also includes basic activities like walking or bending over to pick something up.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_11">• You take IN calories through food and drinks during the day.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_12">CALORIES OUT:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_13">BASAL METABOLIC RATE:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_14">As above, everyone has a Basal Metabolic Rate (BMR). This is the minimum amount of energy your body requires each day simply to live.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_15">Your BMR depends on many factors, including your age and sex. As you get older, your metabolism slows down (your BMR goes down). Furthermore, men tend to have a higher metabolism (BMR) than women.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_16">ACTIVITY LEVEL &amp; EXERCISE:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_17">In addition to your Basal Metabolic Rate, you also burn calories from your daily physical activity.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_18">This will largely depend on what type of job you have, how you spend your days, and how much exercise you get.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_19">• If you spend most of your day sitting at a desk job or watching TV, you will not burn many calories.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_20">• If you do a lot of manual labour or a lot of walking through your day, you will burn more calories.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_21">• If you add formal exercise to your weekly routine, you will burn even more calories!</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_22">CALORIES IN:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_23">As above, pretty much every single thing you eat and drink through your day counts as calories IN (except for things like water, black coffee, or zero-calorie drinks).</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_24">Today, most foods have labels on them that tell you how many calories are in them.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_25">PUTTING IT ALL TOGETHER:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_26">You now know how to calculate how many calories you burn in a day and how many calories you eat. To lose weight, all you have to do is eat less than you burn!</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_27"><b>Aim to eat 500-1000 calories LESS than you burn <u>per day</u>, and that should result in a weight loss of 1-2 pounds per week.</b> For example, if you calculate that you burn 2000 calories in your average day, you need to eat no more than 1500 calories/day in order to lose 1 pound per week.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_28">Keeping a detailed daily Food Log is ESSENTIAL!  Do not try to just guess how many calories you eat each day. <b>You need to track the specific amounts of foods and calories you eat – every little bite, every drink, even the condiments or dressings you add to your foods. You may be surprised just how quickly those calories add up in a day!</b>  Remember to be honest too. Otherwise, you are only cheating yourself …</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_29">To keep a food log, you can simply use the old <u>“pen &amp; paper”</u> method, or you may want to try one of the many <u>online trackers</u> or <u>smartphone apps</u> that are available.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_30">IMPORTANT POINTS:</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_31">• There is no miracle cure or miracle diet for weight loss. Miracle pills or supplements do not exist. Fad diets and detoxes do not work.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_32">• Healthy weight loss that you will keep off takes time. Think of your weight loss journey as a marathon rather than a sprint. You should expect to lose no more than 1-2 pounds per week.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="weight_loss_33">• Weight Loss is 80% diet and 20% exercise. You do not have to be an intense athlete to lose weight. Eating right is the main thing. As you can calculate above,  to lose 150 calories it is much easier to simply not eat 2 cookies, rather than go jogging for 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_34">• Healthy eating is more than just counting calories. For example, it is also important to have a balance of protein, carbohydrates, and fats. However, that goes beyond the scope of this page.</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_35">• If you are truly following the above advice, but feel you are not losing as much weight as you should be, please do not get discouraged. Recent studies are showing that some people actually do not burn calories the same way as the basic math suggests. Stick with it and you will keep losing weight!</string>
    <string name="weight_loss_36">MORE INFORMATION:</string>




    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item>Acne</item>
        <item>Angina</item>
        <item>Annual Physicals</item>
        <item>Asthma</item>
        <item>Back Pain</item>
        <item>Benzodiazepines</item>
        <item>Colon Cancer Screening</item>
        <item>Concussions</item>
        <item>Coughs, Colds &amp; Sore Throats</item>
        <item>Depression</item>
        <item>Diabetes</item>
        <item>Diarrhea</item>
        <item>Ear Infections</item>
        <item>Fever</item>
        <item>Financial Strain</item>
        <item>Headaches</item>
        <item>Heart Attacks</item>
        <item>Liver</item>
        <item>Metamucil</item>
        <item>Osteoporosis</item>
        <item>Pain</item>
        <item>Pink Eye</item>
        <item>Prostate Cancer</item>
        <item>Shingles Vaccine</item>
        <item>Shoulder Pain</item>
        <item>Skin Spots</item>
        <item>Sleep</item>
        <item>Smoking</item>
        <item>Strokes</item>
        <item>Weight Loss</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
